As many office workers adapt to remote work, cities may undergo fundamental change if offices remain under-utilized.
随着许多上班族适应远程办公，如果办公室继续得不到充分利用，城市可能会经历根本性的变化。
Who will benefit if working from home becomes the norm?
如果居家办公成为常态，谁会从中受益？
Employers argue they make considerable savings on real estate when workers shift from office to home work.
雇主们声称，员工从办公室办公转为居家办公时，自己能在房地产上大幅节省开支。
However, these savings result from passing costs on to workers.
然而，这些节省的开支源于把成本转嫁给员工。
Unless employees are fully compensated, this could become a variant of parasitic capitalism, whereby corporate profits increasingly rely on extracting value from the public—and now personal—realm, rather than on generating new value.
除非员工得到充分补偿，否则这可能变成寄生资本主义的一种变体，即企业利润越来越依赖于从公共领域、如今也从个人领域榨取价值，而不是依靠创造新价值。
Though employers are backed by a chorus of remote work advocates, others note the loneliness, reduced productivity and inefficiencies of extended remote work.
尽管雇主得到一众远程办公倡导者的齐声支持，另一些人却指出了长期远程办公存在的孤独感、生产率下降和种种低效问题。
If working from home becomes permanent, employees will have to dedicate part of their private space to work.
如果居家办公成为一种永久性的安排，员工就不得不把自己的一部分私人空间专门用于工作。
This requires purchasing desks, chairs and office equipment.
这就需要购置书桌、椅子和办公设备。
It also means having private space dedicated to work: the space must be heated, cleaned, maintained and paid for.
这还意味着要有专门用于工作的私人空间：必须给这块空间供暖、打扫和维护，还要为它付钱。
The cost depends on many things, but for purposes of illustration, I have run some estimates for Montreal.
这项成本取决于很多因素，但为了举例说明，我针对蒙特利尔做了一些估算。
The exercise is simple but important, since it brings these costs out of the realm of speculation into the realm of meaningful discussion.
这项测算虽然简单，却很重要，因为它把这些成本从猜测的范畴带进了有意义的讨论范畴。
Rough calculations show that the savings made by employers when their staff works from home are of similar value to the compensation workers should receive for setting up offices at home.
粗略计算表明，员工居家办公时雇主节省的开支，与员工因在家设立办公室而应得的补偿价值相近。
What does this mean for offices in cities?
这对城市里的办公室意味着什么？
One of two things may happen: Employers pass these costs on to employees.
可能会出现两种情况，一是雇主把这些成本转嫁给员工。
This would be a form of expropriation, with employees absorbing production costs that have traditionally been paid by the employer.
这将是某种形式的侵占：员工要承担传统上一直由雇主支付的生产成本。
This represents a considerable transfer of value from employees to employers.
这意味着大量价值从员工手中转移到了雇主手中。
When employees are properly compensated, employers’ real estate savings will be modest.
员工一旦得到合理补偿，雇主在房地产上节省的开支就会很有限。
If savings are modest, then the many advantages of working in offices—such as a lively atmosphere, rapidity of communication, team-building and acclimatization of new employees—will encourage employers to shelve the idea of remote work and, like Yahoo in 2013, encourage employees to work most of the time from corporate office space.
如果节省的开支很有限，那么在办公室工作的诸多优势——比如活跃的氛围、快速的沟通、团队建设以及新员工对环境的适应——就会促使雇主搁置远程办公的想法，并像雅虎在2013年那样，鼓励员工大部分时间在公司的办公场所工作。